Yes, thanks a lot for taking my question.
a question on Lekvio in China. Maybe if you could share some details on how the momentum
is developing and what would be needed to really have upside to your current guidance of, I guess,
it's 1 billion in China. Yeah, thank you. Thank you, Erwin, for the question. So, you know,
with Lekvio, we initially saw very strong uptake in launch in the private self-based segment,
which I think really indicates there's a high demand for the medicine in the secondary
prevention, but importantly as well in the primary prevention setting as well from a self-based
standpoint. And then, you know, what I think what we've seen is very strong performance now
in once we had the NRDL, you know, listing, we see that both in the hospital segment and in the
in the traditional segments as well, very strong performance.
So I think,
seeing that continued steady growth should get us to it being our largest medicine potentially that
we've ever delivered in China. And Trusto gives us a very strong benchmark in China, but we think
Lekvio has the potential as well. And I think really it depends now on the dynamics on the
growth as we try to continue to expand into additional hospitals, into additional regions.
I would say as well, we look now to also bring additional SIRNAs into the China market rapidly.
We
think there's an opportunity in cardiovascular hypertension and CVR risk reduction for our
follow-on SIRNAs in China, where there seems to be a high demand for infrequently administered
therapies with very clean safety profiles. And I think that gives us a bigger opportunity in
China in the longer term for that cardiovascular SIRNA portfolio.
Thank you.
Your next question comes from the audience.
The line of Steve Schuyler from TD Cowan. Please go ahead.
Oh, thank you for the follow-up. Were there any surprises in the label or the pricing of the
oral PCSK9 inhibitor recently approved that alter Novartis' view of the commercial potential for
Lekvio? And Vas is a very skilled and experienced drug developer. Any thoughts on how limiting the
fasting ultimately will be? Thank you. Yeah, thanks, Steve. So I think no surprise,